<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
    <amime>
        <shonen>
            <!-- 
                Attack on Titan (Japanese: 進撃の巨人, Hepburn: Shingeki no Kyojin, lit. 'The Advancing Giant') is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Hajime Isayama. 
                It is set in a world where humanity is forced to live in cities surrounded by three enormous walls that protect them from gigantic man-eating humanoids referred to as Titans; 
                the story follows Eren Yeager, who vows to exterminate the Titans after they bring about the destruction of his hometown and the death of his mother. 
                It was serialized in Kodansha's monthly magazine Bessatsu Shōnen Magazine from September 2009 to April 2021, with its chapters collected in 34 tankōbon volumes. 

                An anime television series was produced by Wit Studio (seasons 1–3) and MAPPA (season 4). A 25-episode first season was broadcast from April to September 2013, 
                followed by a 12-episode second season broadcast from April to June 2017. A 22-episode third season was broadcast in two parts, with the first 12 episodes airing 
                from July to October 2018 and the last 10 episodes airing from April to July 2019. A fourth and final season premiered in December 2020, airing 16 episodes in its first part. 
                A second part consisting of 12 episodes aired from January to April 2022, and a third and final part will air in two halves; the first half will premiere in March 2023.

                Attack on Titan has become a critical and commercial success. As of September 2022, the manga had over 110 million copies in circulation, 
                making it one of the best-selling manga series of all time. It has won several awards, including the Kodansha Manga Award, the Attilio Micheluzzi Award, and the Harvey Award. 
             -->
            <name>
                <english>Attack on titan</english>
                <japanese>Shingeki no Kyojin</japanese>
            </name>
            <season>4</season>
            <author>Hajime Isayama</author>
            <genre>
                <list>Action</list>
                <list>Dark fantasy</list>
                <list>Post-apocalyptic</list>
            </genre>
            <date_publish>
                <season_1> 
                    <year_started>2013</year_started>
                    <month_started>April</month_started>
                <!--<month_ended>September</month_ended>-->
                </season_1>
                <season_2> 
                    <year_started>2017</year_started>
                    <month_started>April</month_started>
               <!--<month_ended>June</month_ended>-->
                </season_2>
                <season_3> 
                    <part_1>
                        <year_started>2018</year_started>
                        <month_started>July</month_started>
                    <!--<month_ended>October</month_ended>-->
                    </part_1>
                    <part_2>
                        <year_started>2019</year_started>
                        <month_started>April</month_started>
                    <!--<month_ended>July</month_ended>-->
                    </part_2>
                </season_3>
                <season_4> 
                    <part_1>
                        <year_started>2020</year_started>
                        <month_started>December</month_started>
                    <!--<year_ended>2021</year_ended>
                        <month_ended>March</month_ended>-->
                    </part_1>
                    <part_2>
                        <year_started>2022</year_started>
                        <month_started>January</month_started>
                    <!--<month_ended>April</month_ended>-->
                    </part_2>
                <!-- <part_3>
                        Not started yet
                    </part_3> -->
                </season_4>
            </date_publish>
            <episode>
                <season_1>25</season_1>
                <season_2>12</season_2>
                <season_3>
                    <part_1>12</part_1>
                    <part_2>10</part_2>
                </season_3>
                <season_4>
                    <part_1>16</part_1>
                    <part_1>12</part_1>
                <!--<part_3>Not available yet</part_3>-->
                </season_4>
            </episode>
            <synopsis>
            The story of Attack on Titan centers on a civilization inside three circular walls. According to the knowledge propagated locally,
            it is the last surviving vestige of human civilization. Its inhabitants, known as Eldians, have been led to believe that over one hundred years ago,
            humanity was driven to the brink of extinction after the emergence of humanoid giants called Titans, who attack and eat humans on sight.
            The last remnants of humanity retreated behind three concentric walls and enjoyed roughly a century of peace. 
            Within the walls, the thought of venturing outside is strongly frowned upon and discouraged. To combat Titans, 
            the country's military employs Vertical Maneuvering Equipment (VME), also called Omni-Directional Maneuvering Gear (ODM Gear): 
            a set of waist-mounted grappling hooks and gas-powered propulsion enabling immense mobility in three dimensions. 
            Swords made of ultrahard steel are used in conjunction with the gear, and eventually rocket launcher-like weapons called Thunder Spears are also developed. 
            There exist different types of Titans. Pure Titans are the weakest and most generic Titans, whose behavior is easy to predict, making them easy to kill. 
            Abnormal Titans are Pure Titans whose behavior is more difficult to predict, making them far more dangerous. 
            The Nine Titans, also known as Titan Shifters (Attack, Colossal, Armored, Female, Beast, Jaw, Cart, War Hammer, and Founding), 
            are the strongest Titans; each is able to shift back and forth between human and Titan form to access their Titan's abilities. 
            Many Titan Shifters also possess the ability to harden certain parts of their bodies at will, typically in order to make them virtually impenetrable, or to strengthen their blows during combat. 
            Pure Titans are created by injecting Eldians with Pure Titan spinal fluid. If a Pure Titan eats the human body of a person who possesses one of the Nine Titans, 
            said Eldian will revert to human form and gain that Shifter's powers, whereupon they are cursed to live only 13 more years. 
            If their powers are not inherited by another Eldian before their death, their powers will be inherited by an Eldian baby born shortly thereafter, 
            regardless of distance or blood-relations. As the story progresses, the true nature of the Titans and the existence of civilization outside the walls is revealed to the characters and the audience.
            </synopsis>
        </shonen>

        <shojo>
            
            <date_publish>
            </date_publish>
            <season>
            </season>
        </shojo>

        <seinen>
            <date_publish>
            </date_publish>
            <season>
            </season>
        </seinen>

        <josei>
            <date_publish>
            </date_publish>
            <season>
            </season>
        </josei>
        
        <kodomomuke>
            <date_publish>
            </date_publish>
            <season>
            </season>
        </kodomomuke>

    </anime>